Architecture Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Renaissance Italy (Box 26)
  - Cities (Box 27)
    - Venice (Box 33)
      - Synagogues (Box 34)
      - Squares (Box 34)
        - Piazza S. Marco (Box 34)
          - Clock Tower (Box 34)
          - Logetta (Box 34)
        - Piazzetta (Box 34)
    - Verona [Slide box 201] (Box 34)
    - Vicenza (Box 34)
      - Loggia (Box 34)
      - Palaces (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Chiericati (Museo Civico) (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Iseppo da Porto (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Municipale (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Porto-Barbaro (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Porto Breganze (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Porto Festa (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Ragione (Basilica) (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Valmarana (Box 34)
        - Palazzo Thiene [Slide box 202] (Box 34)
      - Theaters (Box 34)
        - Teatro Olimpico (Box 34)
      - Villas (Box 34)
        - Villa Capra (Rotunda) (Box 34)
          - Exterior (Box 34)
          - Interior [Slide boxes 202-203] (Box 34)
    - Vignardolo di Monticello [Slide box 203] (Box 34)
- Renaissance Poland (Box 34)
  - Various (Box 34)
- Renaissance Portugal (Box 34)
  - Aveiro (Box 34)
  - Belem (Box 34)
    - Monastery of S. Maria (Box 34)
    - Tower of Belem (Torre de Belem) (Box 34)
  - Braga (Box 34)
  - Cochin, India (Box 34)
  - Coimbra (Box 34)
    - Churches (Box 34)
      - New Cathedral (Box 34)
      - S. Cruz (Box 34)
    - Schools [Slide box 204] (Box 34)
      - University (Box 34)
  - Guarda (Box 34)
  - Lisbon (Box 34)
    - Churches (Box 34)
      - S. Antonio da Se (Box 34)
  - Old Goa, India (Box 34)
  - Oporto (Box 34)
    - Churches (Box 34)
      - Church of the Carmo (Box 34)
      - Church of the Clerigos (Box 34)
      - S. Francisco (Box 34)
  - Ponta Delgada, Azores (Box 34)
  - Queluz (Box 34)
  - Tomar (Box 34)
  - Viana do Castelo [Slide box 205] (Box 35)
  - Vila do Conde (Box 35)
- Renaissance Russia (Box 35)
  - Berezouets (Box 35)
  - Dubrovitsi (Box 35)
  - Dyakovo (Box 35)
  - Fili (Box 35)
  - Kizhi (Box 35)
  - Kolomenskoe (Box 35)
  - Kuzmini (Box 35)
  - Leningrad (Box 35)
    - Plans (Box 35)
    - Churches (Box 35)
      - Church of SS. Peter and Paul [Slide box 206] (Box 35)
    - Government Buildings (Box 35)
      - Admiralty (Box 35)
    - Palaces (Box 35)
      - Tauride Palace (Box 35)
      - Peterhof (Box 35)
  - Moscow (Box 35)
    - Churches (Box 35)
      - Kremlin (Box 35)
        - Churches (Box 35)
          - Cathedral of the Annunciation [Slide boxes 206-207] (Box 35)
          - Cathedral of Archangel Michael [Slide box 207] (Box 35)
          - Cathedral of the Assumption (Box 35)
        - Palaces (Box 35)
          - Teremnoi Dvoret Garret Palace (Box 35)
  - Nekolskoe (Box 35)
  - Nenoksa (Box 35)
  - Novgorod (Box 35)
  - Ostankino (Box 35)
  - Ostrov (Box 35)
  - Panilovo (Box 35)
  - Pavlovsk (Box 35)
  - Staraya Ladoga (Box 35)
  - Tsarkoe Seloe (Box 35)
  - Varzug (Box 35)
  - Vladimir (Box 35)
  - Yadrovo (Box 35)
  - Yalta (Box 35)
  - Zagorsk [Slide boxes 207-208] (Box 35)
  - Zvenigorod [Slide box 208] (Box 35)
- Renaissance Spain (Box 35)
  - General (Box 35)
  - Architects (Box 35)
    - Gil de Hontanon (Box 35)
  - Cities (Box 35)
    - Alcala de Henares (Box 35)
    - Barcelona (Box 35)
    - Belmonte (Box 35)
    - Burgos (Box 35)
    - Cadiz (Box 35)
      - Cathedral (Box 35)
        - Exterior (Box 35)
        - Interior (Box 35)
      - Our Lady of Carmen (Box 35)
      - S. Lorenzo (Box 35)
  - Carmona (Box 35)
  - Cordoba (Box 35)
    - Churches [Slide box 209] (Box 35)
      - Cathedral (Box 35)
      - Convento de la Merced (Box 35)
      - Ermita de La Alegria (Box 35)
      - S. Catalina (Box 35)
      - S. Hipolito (Box 35)
      - S. Pablo (Box 35)
    - Hospitals (Box 35)
    - Palaces (Box 35)
  - Ecija (Box 35)
  - El Pardo (Box 35)
  - El Paular (Box 35)
  - Escorial (Box 35)
    - Exterior [Slide boxes 209-210] (Box 35)
      - South Façade [Slide box 210] (Box 35)
      - Towers (Box 35)
    - Interior (Box 35)
    - Church of S. Lorenzo (Box 35)
      - Exterior (Box 35)
      - Interior (Box 35)
        - Main Retablo (Box 35)
        - Sacristy [Slide box 211] (Box 36)
        - Galeria Convalecientes (Box 36)
        - Pantheon de los Reyes (Box 36)
        - Patio de los Evangelista (Box 36)
        - Patio de la Portena (Box 36)
        - Patio de los Reyes (Box 36)
        - Small Palace Courtyard (Box 36)
  - Estepa (Box 36)
  - Fernan Nunez (Box 36)
  - Granada (Box 36)
    - Churches (Box 36)
      - Cathedral (Box 36)
        - Exterior (Box 36)
        - Interior (Box 36)
          - Retablo of Santiago [Slide box 212] (Box 36)
          - Rotunda (Box 36)
          - Capilla Real (Box 36)
          - Chapel of Nuestra Senora la Antigua (Box 36)
          - Sagrario (Box 36)
      - Cartuja (Box 36)
        - Interior (Box 36)
          - Sacristy (Box 36)
          - Sagrario Chapel (Box 36)
      - La Magdalena (Box 36)
      - Nuestra Señora (Box 36)
      - S. Ana (Box 36)
      - SS. Bartome and Santiago (Box 36)
      - S. Domingo [Slide box 213] (Box 36)
        - Interior (Box 36)
          - Camarin (Box 36)
          - Retablo de Rosario (Box 36)
      - S. Felipe Neri (Box 36)
      - S. Jeronimo (Box 36)
      - S. Juan de Dios (Box 36)
      - SS. Justo y Pastor (Box 36)
    - Hospitals (Box 36)
    - Palaces (Box 36)
      - Palace of Charles V (Box 36)
        - Exterior (Box 36)
          - South Façade (Box 36)
          - West Façade (Box 36)
        - Interior [Slide box 214] (Box 36)
        - Courtyard (Box 36)
  - Guadalajara (Box 36)
  - Guadulupe (Box 36)
  - Guadix (Box 36)
  - Jerez de la Frontera (Box 36)
    - Churches (Box 36)
      - Cartuja (Box 36)
      - Collegiate Church (Box 36)
      - Church of S. Miguel (Box 36)
  - La Granja (Box 36)
  - Lerma (Box 36)
    - Palaces (Box 36)
    - Plazas (Box 36)
  - Loro Del Rio (Box 36)
  - Loyola (Box 36)
  - Lucena (Box 36)
    - Churches (Box 36)
      - S. Juan de Dios (Box 36)
      - S. Mateo [Slide box 215] (Box 36)
  - Madrid (Box 36)
    - Churches (Box 36)
      - Convent of Montserrat (Box 36)
      - Descalzas Reales (Box 36)
        - Staircase (Box 36)
        - Upper Cloister (Box 36)
      - Ermita Del Puerto (Box 36)
    - Government Buildings (Box 36)
    - Hospitals (Box 36)
    - Palaces (Box 36)
      - Buen Retiro (Box 36)
      - Royal Palace (Box 36)
        - Exterior [Slide boxes 215-216] (Box 36)
        - Interior [Slide box 216] (Box 36)
  - Malaga (Box 36)
    - Churches (Box 36)
      - La Victoria (Box 36)
        - Camarin (Box 36)
        - Crypt (Box 36)
  - Mombeltran (Box 36)
  - Murcia (Box 36)
  - Palma de Mallorca (Box 36)
  - Priego (Box 36)
    - Churches (Box 36)
      - Church of the Augustias (Box 36)
      - Church of the Aurora (Box 36)
      - El Carmen (Box 36)
      - Las Mercedes (Box 36)
      - Parish Church (Box 36)
        - Sagrario Chapel and Gallery (Box 36)
      - S. Francisco [Slide boxes 216-217] (Box 36–37)
        - Capilla Jesus Nazareno [Slide box 217] (Box 37)
      - S. Juan de Dios (Box 37)
        - Fountains (Box 37)
  - Puerto Real (Box 37)
  - Salamanca (Box 37)
  - Santiago de Compostella (Box 37)
  - Seville (Box 37)
    - Churches (Box 37)
      - Cathedral [Slide boxes 217-218] (Box 37)
      - S. Luis [Slide box 218] (Box 37)
        - Exterior (Box 37)
        - Interior (Box 37)
      - Episcopal Palace, Archbishop Palace (Box 37)
    - Schools (Box 37)
      - Town Hall (Box 37)
  - Toledo (Box 37)
    - Churches (Box 37)
      - Cathedral (Box 37)
      - S. Juan Bautista (Box 37)
    - Government Buildings (Box 37)
    - Hospitals (Box 37)
      - S. Juan Bautista (Box 37)
    - Palaces (Box 37)
      - Alcazar (Box 37)
  - Ubeda [Slide boxes 218-219] (Box 37)
  - Umbrete [Slide box 219] (Box 37)
  - Valencia (Box 37)
  - Valladolid (Box 37)
  - Velez Blanco (Box 37)
  - Yuste (Box 37)
  - Zaragoza (Box 37)
- Renaissance Latin America (Box 37)
  - Renaissance Argentina (Box 37)
    - Buenos Aires (Box 37)
    - Candongo (Box 37)
    - Cochinoca (Box 37)
    - Cordoba (Box 37)
    - Lujan (Box 37)
    - Purmamarca (Box 37)
    - Salta (Box 37)
    - San Ignacio (Box 37)
    - San Isidro (Box 37)
    - Santa Catalina (Box 37)
    - Santa Fe (Box 37)
    - Tucuman (Box 37)
    - Uquia (Box 37)
  - Renaissance Bolivia (Box 37)
    - Various (Box 37)
  - Renaissance Brazil (Box 37)
    - Bahia [Slide box 220] (Box 37)
      - Church of Carmo (Box 37)
      - Igreja da Se (Box 37)
      - Pelourinho (Box 37)
      - S. Francisco (Box 37)
        - Exterior (Box 37)
        - Interior (Box 37)
    - Congonhas do Campo (Box 37)
    - Ouro Preto (Box 37)
      - Churches (Box 37)
        - S. Francisco de Assis [Slide box 221] (Box 37)
    - Recife (Box 37)
    - Rio de Janeiro (Box 37)
    - Sabara (Box 37)
    - S. Joao del Rei (Box 37)
    - Sao Salvador (Box 37)
  - Renaissance Chile (Box 37)
    - Various (Box 37)
  - Renaissance Colombia (Box 37)
    - Bogota (Box 37)
    - Cartagena (Box 37)
  - Renaissance Ecuador (Box 37)
    - Quito (Box 37)
      - Churches (Box 37)
        - La Compania [Slide boxes 221-222] (Box 37)
        - S. Francisco [Slide box 222] (Box 37)
  - Renaissance Guatemala (Box 37)
    - Antigua (Box 37)
  - Renaissance Mexico (Box 37)
    - Acambaro (Box 37)
    - Acapulco (Box 37)
    - Acatepec (Box 37)
    - Acatlan (Box 37)
    - Acatzingo (Box 37)
    - Acolman (Box 37)
      - S. Augustin (Box 37)
        - Exterior (Box 37)
        - Interior (Box 37)
        - Cloisters [Slide box 223] (Box 37)
    - Actopan (Box 37)
    - Acultzingo (Box 37)
    - Aguas Calientes (Box 37)
    - Alvarado (Box 37)
    - Anagahua (Box 37)
    - Apam (Box 37)
    - Aranza (Box 37)
    - Atlatlaucan (Box 37)
    - Atlixco (Box 37)
    - Atotonilco de Grande [Slide boxes 223-224] (Box 37)
    - Atotonilco de Tula [Slide box 224] (Box 37)
    - Atzcapotzalco (Box 37)
    - Calpan (Box 37)
    - Campeche (Box 37)
    - Chiapa de Corzo (Box 37)
    - Chignahuapan (Box 37)
    - Chihuahua (Box 37)
    - Chimalhuacan (Box 37)
    - Cholula (Box 37)
      - Maps and Plans (Box 37)
      - Churches (Box 37)
        - S. Gabriel (Royal Chapel) (Box 37)
    - Churubusco [Slide box 225] (Box 37)
    - Coixtlahuaca (Box 37)
    - Coyoacan (Box 37)
    - Cuauhtinchan (Box 37)
    - Cuernavaca (Box 37)
      - Churches (Box 37)
        - Cathedral (Box 37)
          - Plans and Drawings (Box 37)
          - Exterior (Box 37)
          - Interior (Box 37)
      - Palaces (Box 37)
        - Palace of Cortez (State Palace) (Box 37)
    - Cuitzeo (Box 38)
    - Culhuacan [Slide box 226] (Box 38)
    - Dolores Hidalgo (Box 38)
    - Durango (Box 38)
    - Dzemul (Box 38)
    - Dzibilchaltun (Box 38)
    - El Sitio (Box 38)
    - Epazoyucan (Box 38)
    - Erongaricuaro (Box 38)
    - Etla (Box 38)
    - Etzatlan (Box 38)
    - Guadalajara (Box 38)
    - Guadalupe (Box 38)
    - Guanajuato (Box 38)
      - Churches (Box 38)
        - La Compania (Box 38)
        - S. Diego of Acala [Slide box 227] (Box 38)
        - La Valenciana (S. Cayetano) (Box 38)
    - Haumantla (Box 38)
    - Huaquechula (Box 38)
    - Huatlatlauhca (Box 38)
    - Huejotzingo [Slide boxes 227-228] (Box 38)
    - Huezotla [Slide box 228] (Box 38)
    - Huitzo (Box 38)
    - Ixmiquilpan (Box 38)
    - Izamal (Box 38)
    - Jacona (Box 38)
    - Janitzio Island Michoacan (Box 38)
    - Jilotepec (Box 38)
    - Jolalpan (Box 38)
    - Lagos de Moreno (Box 38)
    - Malinalco (Box 38)
    - Mani (Box 38)
    - Merida [Slide box 229] (Box 39)
    - Metztitlan (Box 39)
    - Mexico City (Box 39)
      - Maps/Plans (Box 39)
        - Plan of 1563 (Box 39)
        - Plan of 1596 (Box 39)
      - Churches (Box 39)
        - Cathedral and Sagrario [Slide boxes 229-230] (Box 39)
          - Cathedral [Slide box 230] (Box 39)
            - Plans and Drawings (Box 39)
              - Exterior (Box 39)
              - Interior (Box 39)
          - Sagrario (Box 39)
        - Corpus Christi (Box 39)
        - Jesus Maria (Box 39)
        - La Ensenanza [Slide box 231] (Box 39)
        - La Merced (Box 39)
        - La Profesa (Box 39)
        - S. Bernardo (Box 39)
        - S. Brigidia (Box 39)
        - S. Diminigo (Box 39)
        - S. Hipolito (Box 39)
        - S. Inez (Box 39)
        - S. Jose de Gracia (Box 39)
        - S. Jose de los Naturales (Box 39)
        - S. Juan de Dios (Box 39)
        - Santisima (Box 39)
      - Government Buildings (Box 39)
      - Houses [Slide boxes 231-232] (Box 39)
        - Calimaya [Slide box 232] (Box 39)
        - House of Jose Borda (Box 39)
      - Palaces (Box 39)
      - Schools (Box 39)
        - Collegio de San Ildefonso (Box 39)
        - Las Vizcainas (Box 39)
      - Squares (Box 39)
    - Meztitlan (Box 39)
    - Mixtepec (Box 39)
    - Molango (Box 39)
    - Morelia (Box 39)
      - Churches (Box 39)
        - Convent of la Compania (Box 39)
        - Cathedral [Slide box 233] (Box 39)
    - Oaxaca (Box 39)
      - Cathedral (Box 39)
      - La Soledad (Box 39)
      - S. Augustin (Box 39)
      - S. Domingo (Box 39)
        - Exterior (Box 39)
        - Interior (Box 39)
        - Cloisters (Box 39)
    - Oaxtepec (Box 39)
    - Ocotepec (Box 39)
    - Ocotlan (Box 39)
    - Ocuituco (Box 39)
    - Orizaba (Box 39)
    - Otumba (Box 39)
      - Pachuguilla (Box 39)
    - Papalotla [Slide box 234] (Box 39)
    - Patzcuaro (Box 39)
    - Puebla (Box 39)
      - Churches (Box 39)
        - Cathedral (Box 39)
          - Exterior (Box 39)
          - Interior (Box 39)
        - La Compania (Box 39)
        - N.S. Del Carmen (Box 39)
        - S. Cristobal (Box 39)
        - S. Domingo [Slide boxes 234-235] (Box 39–40)
        - S. Francisco [Slide box 235] (Box 40)
        - S. Jose (Box 40)
        - Santa Monica (Box 40)
          - Houses (Box 40)
            - Casa de Alfenique (Box 40)
            - Casa de los Munecos (Box 40)
            - Casa Del Dean Thomas (Box 40)
    - Quecholac (Box 40)
    - Queretaro (Box 40)
      - Churches (Box 40)
        - Convent of S. Augustin (Box 40)
        - Convent Church of S. Clara (Box 40)
        - S. Francisco (Box 40)
        - Santa Rosa (Box 40)
        - Convent of S. Rosa de Viterbo [Slide box 236] (Box 40)
    - Salamanca (Box 40)
    - Saltillo (Box 40)
    - San Angel (Box 40)
    - San Cristobal las Casas (Box 40)
    - S. Luis Potosi (Box 40)
    - S. Martin Texmelucan (Box 40)
    - S. Miguel Allende (Box 40)
    - Tacuba (Box 40)
    - Taxco [Slide boxes 236-237] (Box 40)
    - Tecali [Slide box 237] (Box 40)
    - Tecamalchalco (Box 40)
    - Tecpatan, Chiapas (Box 40)
    - Tecozautla (Box 40)
    - Tehuacan (Box 40)
    - Tepalcingo (Box 40)
    - Tepeaca (Box 40)
    - Tepeapulco (Box 40)
    - Tepeji del Rio (Box 40)
    - Tepeyango (Box 40)
    - Teposcolula (Box 40)
    - Tepotzotlan [Slide box 238] (Box 40)
      - S. Francisco Xavier (Box 40)
        - Exterior (Box 40)
        - Interior (Box 40)
          - Retablos (Box 40)
    - Tepoztlan, Morelos (Box 40)
    - Texcoco (Box 40)
    - Tezontepec (Box 40)
    - Ticul (Box 40)
    - Tipeojuma (Box 40)
    - Tiripitio (Box 40)
    - Tizatlan (Box 40)
    - Tlachichilco (Box 40)
    - Tlacolula (Box 40)
    - Tlacotepec (Box 40)
    - Tlahuac (Box 40)
    - Tlahuelilpa (Box 40)
    - Tlalmanalco [Slide boxes 238-239] (Box 40)
    - Tlalnepantla [Slide box 239] (Box 40)
    - Tlalpujahua (Box 40)
    - Tlaltenango (Box 40)
    - Tlamaco (Box 40)
    - Tlaquiltenango (Box 40)
    - Tlatelolco (Box 40)
    - Tlaxcala (Box 40)
      - Churches (Box 40)
        - Sanctuary of Ocotlan (Box 40)
    - Tlaxcalazingo (Box 40)
    - Tlaxiaco (Box 40)
    - Tlayacapan (Box 40)
    - Tochimilco [Slide boxes 239-240] (Box 40)
    - Toluca [Slide box 240] (Box 40)
    - Tonanzintla (Box 40)
    - Totimehuacan (Box 40)
    - Totolapan (Box 40)
    - Totolinga (Box 40)
    - Tula (Box 40)
    - Tzicatlan (Box 40)
    - Tzintzintzan (Box 40)
    - Uman (Box 40)
    - Uruapan (Box 40)
    - Xaracuaro (Box 40)
    - Xochimilco (Box 40)
    - Yanhuitlan (Box 40)
    - Yecapixtla [Slide boxes 240-241] (Box 40–41)
    - Yururia [Slide box 241] (Box 41)
    - Zacapu (Box 41)
    - Zacatecas (Box 41)
    - Zacatlan de la Manzanas (Box 41)
    - Zempoala (Box 41)
    - Zinacautepec (Box 41)
  - Renaissance Panama (Box 41)
    - Various (Box 41)
  - Renaissance Paraguay (Box 41)
    - Various (Box 41)
  - Renaissance Peru [Slide boxes 241-242] (Box 41)
    - Arequipa [Slide box 242] (Box 41)
    - Cuzco (Box 41)
    - Juli (Box 41)
    - Lima (Box 41)
      - Churches (Box 41)
        - Cathedral (Box 41)
        - La Merced (Box 41)
        - S. Augustin (Box 41)
        - S. Francisco [Slide boxes 242-243] (Box 41)
      - Hospitals [Slide box 243] (Box 41)
    - Puno (Box 41)
    - Pupuja (Box 41)
    - Sana (Box 41)
    - Yanahuara (Box 41)
  - Renaissance Venezuela (Box 41)
    - Caracas (Box 41)
- Renaissance Caribbean (Box 41)
  - Renaissance Cuba (Box 41)
    - Havana (Box 41)
    - Santiago de Cuba (Box 41)
  - Renaissance Dominican Republic (Box 41)
    - Santo Domingo (Box 41)
  - Renaissance Puerto Rico (Box 41)
    - San Juan (Box 41)
  - Renaissance El Salvador (Box 41)
    - Pedro Guerrero (Box 41)
    - San Vicente (Box 41)
- 20th Century Architecture (Box 41)
  - Africa (Box 41)
    - Libya (Box 41)
    - Mauritania (Box 41)
    - Morocco (Box 41)
    - Senegal (Box 41)
    - South Africa [Slide box 244] (Box 41)
  - Albania (Box 41)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 41)
  - Andorra (Box 41)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 41)
  - Australia (Box 41)
    - Canberra (Box 41)
    - Sydney (Box 41)
  - Austria (Box 41)
    - Architects (Box 41)
      - Bauer, Leopold (Box 41)
      - Coop Himmelblau (Box 41)
      - Deininger, Wunibald (Box 41)
      - Engelmann, Paul (Box 41)
      - Felgel, Oskar (Box 41)
      - Hoffmann, Josef (Box 41)
      - Hoppe, Emil (Box 41)
      - Loos, Adolf [Slide boxes 244-245] (Box 41)
      - Margold, E.J. [Slide box 245] (Box 41)
      - Plecnik, Josef (Box 41)
      - Schonthal, Otto (Box 41)
      - Sitte, Camillo (Box 41)
      - Wagner, Otto (Box 41)
        - Wagnerschule Project (Box 41)
      - Wiener Wekstatte (Box 41)
    - Cities (Box 41)
      - Aue (Box 41)
      - Bregenz (Box 41)
      - Graz-Eggenberg (Box 41)
      - Hohenberg (Box 41)
      - Jagerndorf (Box 41)
      - Linz (Box 41)
      - Payerbach (Box 41)
      - Salzburg (Box 41)
      - Vienna [Slide boxes 245-246] (Box 41)
        - Banks [Slide box 246] (Box 41)
          - Austrian Land Bank (Box 41)
          - Central Savings Bank (Favoriten Branch) (Box 41)
        - Bridges (Box 41)
        - Churches (Box 41)
          - Ste Inhofkirche (Box 41)
          - Votice Church (Box 41)
        - Exhibitions (Box 41)
        - Gates (Box 41)
        - Government Buildings (Box 41)
          - Imperial Forum [Slide box 247] (Box 42)
          - Postal Savings Bank (Box 42)
          - Rathaus (Box 42)
        - Hospitals (Box 42)
          - Purkersdorf Sanatorium (Box 42)
          - Tower of Fools (Narrenturm) (Box 42)
        - Houses- Apartments (Box 42)
          - Freud's Apartment at Berggasse 19 (Box 42)
          - Adolf Loos Apartment (Box 42)
          - Hundertwasserhaus (Box 42)
          - Majolika House (Box 42)
          - Miethaus Linke Wienzeile 38 [Slide box 248] (Box 42)
          - Stadiongasse Buildings (Box 42)
        - Houses- Residential (Box 42)
          - Edward Ast House (Box 42)
          - Brauner House (Box 42)
          - Henneberg Villa (Box 42)
          - Villa Herman Bahr (Box 42)
          - Horner House (Box 42)
          - Knips House (Box 42)
          - 2nd Moll House (Box 42)
          - Moser House (Box 42)
          - Moller House (Box 42)
          - Rufer House (Box 42)
          - Town House on Rennewegstrasse (Box 42)
          - Skywa-Primavesti Villa (Box 42)
          - "Standard Steel" House (Box 42)
          - Steiner House (Box 42)
          - Strasser House [Slide box 249] (Box 42)
          - Stross House (Box 42)
          - Wagner Villa (Box 42)
          - Wagner House (Box 42)
          - Wittgenstein House (Box 42)
          - Wildbrandtgasse House (Box 42)
        - Housing (Box 42)
          - Engelsplatz (Box 42)
          - Fuchsenfeldhof (Box 42)
          - Heiligenstadt (Box 42)
          - Lindenhof (Box 42)
          - Reumanhof (Box 42)
          - Werkbund (Box 42)
        - Museums [Slide box 250] (Box 42)
          - Secession Building (Box 42)
        - Beethoven Exhibit (Box 42)
        - Office Buildings (Box 42)
        - Palaces (Box 42)
        - Restaurants (Box 42)
          - American Bar (Box 42)
        - Schools (Box 42)
        - Stations (Box 42)
          - Karlsplatz Pavilion (Box 42)
        - Stores (Box 42)
          - Goldman and Salatsch Building (Box 42)
          - Retti Candle Shop [Slide box 251] (Box 42)
          - Schullin 1 and 2 (Box 42)
        - Synagogues (Box 42)
        - Theaters (Box 42)
  - Bangladesh (Box 42)
    - Dacca (Box 42)
  - Belgium (Box 42)
    - Averbeke, Em. Van (Box 42)
    - Culot, Maurice (Box 42)
    - Antwerp (Box 42)
    - Brussels (Box 42)
      - Airports (Box 42)
      - Exhibitions [Slide box 252] (Box 42)
        - World Exposition 1958 (Box 42)
          - Atomium (Box 42)
          - Canada (Box 42)
          - France (Box 42)
          - West Germany (Box 42)
          - Philips (Box 42)
          - U.S. (Box 42)
      - Government Buildings (Box 42)
        - Palais de Justice (Box 42)
      - Hospitals (Box 42)
      - Houses-Residential (Box 42)
        - Ambiorix Square (Box 42)
        - Hotel Hallet (Box 42)
        - Hotel Horta [Slide box 253] (Box 43)
        - Hotel Solvay (Box 43)
        - Hotel Stoclet (Box 43)
        - Hotel Tassel (Box 43)
        - Hotel van Eetvelde (Box 43)
      - Office Buildings (Box 43)
        - Maison du Peuple [Slide boxes 253-254] (Box 43)
        - Schools [Slide box 254] (Box 43)
        - Squares (Box 43)
        - Stores (Box 43)
        - Theaters (Box 43)
    - Ghent (Box 43)
    - Saint-Gilles (Box 43)
    - Uccle (Box 43)
  - Britain (Box 43)
    - Architects (Box 43)
      - Archigram (Box 43)
      - Butterfield, WM. (Box 43)
      - Chermayeff, Serge (Box 43)
      - Cockerell, C.R. [Slide box 255] (Box 43)
      - Gandy, Joseph M. (Box 43)
      - Future Systems (Box 43)
      - Gray, Eileen (Box 43)
      - Hadid, Zaha (Box 43)
      - Howard, Ebenezer (Box 43)
      - Jones, Owen (Box 43)
      - Lutyens, Edwin L. (Box 43)
      - Mackintosh, Charles Rennie (Box 43)
      - Own, Robert (Box 43)
      - Pike, Alexander (Box 43)
      - Pugin, A. Welby [Slide box 256] (Box 43)
        - Contrasts (Box 43)
        - Ecclesiastical Ornament (Box 43)
      - Slater, William (Box 43)
      - Soane, Sir John (Box 43)
      - Stirling, James [Slide boxes 256-257] (Box 43)
      - Unwin, Raymond [Slide box 257] (Box 43)
      - Voysey, C.F.A. (Box 43)
    - Places (Box 43)
      - Alton Towers (Box 43)
      - Alvechurch (Box 43)
      - Ashby St. Ledgers (Box 43)
      - Barnard Castle (Box 43)
      - Bath (Box 43)
      - Bear Wood (Box 43)
      - Bedford Park (Box 43)
      - Belsay Castle (Box 43)
      - Berrydown Court (Box 43)
      - Bexley Heath (Box 43)
      - Bexhill-on-Sea [Slide box 258] (Box 43)
      - Bingley (Box 43)
      - Birmingham (Box 43)
      - Bodnant, Wales (Box 43)
      - Bradford (Box 43)
      - Brighton (Box 43)
        - Royal Pavilion (Box 43)
      - Bristol (Box 43)
      - Broad Campden, Glos. (Box 43)
      - Broadleys on Lake Windemere (Box 43)
      - Brockhampton (Box 43)
      - Bromley Palace (Box 43)
      - Bryanston (Box 43)
      - Butterton (Box 43)
      - Buxton (Box 43)
      - Camberley (Box 43)
      - Cambridge [Slide box 259] (Box 44)